<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Alex Su ⌗ personal</title>
    <link>https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Alex Su ⌗ personal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 17:46:20 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT, LLMs and Black Boxes</title>
      <link>https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/chatgpt-gpt3-llm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 17:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/chatgpt-gpt3-llm/</guid>
      <description>Large language models (LLMs) like GPT-3 can be incredibly helpful tools for generating text quickly and accurately. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that LLMs are not sentient beings and they don&amp;rsquo;t truly understand the meaning behind the language they generate. Instead, they use mathematical models to predict the most likely response based on their training data. To use LLMs effectively, it&amp;rsquo;s important to be mindful of the data that&amp;rsquo;s being used to train them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install chromium on Mac M1 using homebrew</title>
      <link>https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/install-chromium-on-mac-m1-usgin-brew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 18:30:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/install-chromium-on-mac-m1-usgin-brew/</guid>
      <description>It not as easy as it seems on first look, but:
zsh brew install --cask chromium sudo xattr -r -d com.apple.quarantine /Applications/Chromium.app </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Avoid When You Do Job Test</title>
      <link>https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/what-to-avoid-when-you-do-job-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 18:30:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/what-to-avoid-when-you-do-job-test/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been interviewing software developers for 11 years, and for the last four years, I&amp;rsquo;ve averaged 1-2 interviews each week. We normally don&amp;rsquo;t send a test to persons whose experience we can readily validate in an interview or through a background check, but it is OK to send a test to applicants with no or little experience. From start to finish, the test usually takes less than 4 hours to construct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How This Site Made and Site Generators</title>
      <link>https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/how-this-site-made-and-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 22:18:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alex-y-su.github.io/alex-su.github.io/posts/how-this-site-made-and-site-generators/</guid>
      <description>The older I become, the less I seek for the most innovative answers. Some solutions should suffice, even if they are far from flawless.
For a website with dynamic material, such as a blog or personal page, generation is not required. Also, it is preferable not to pay wherever possible (there is always a better place to use your money than Amazon or your domestic hosting provider).
HUGO (https://gohugo.io) generates this side statically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
